Hello Git and GitHub

This is a homework project for codecademy to build on my knowledge of javascript. 
The program is a javascript based program that should output a random story idea 
with a genre, gender, name and plot device (force) the character fights to get your 
creative juices going. Its very simple and should return a single sentence with 
randomized choices from the arrays at the top.
